Guide to the Christian Conference of Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Related Organizations / Conferences, Series VII
  - World Council of Churches/Pontifical Commission Justice and Peace: Committee on Society, Peace, and Development, Fascicle 1-3 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - World Council of Churches/Pontifical Commission Justice and Peace: Committee on Society, Peace, and Development, Fascicle 4 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - World Council of Churches: Programme to Combat Racism, 1984-1990 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - World Council of Churches: Programme to Combat Racism, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - World Council of Churches: Programme Unit Education and Communication, 1965-1972 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - World Council of Churches: Programme Unit on Education and Renewal, 1987-1990 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - World Council of Churches: Programme Unit on Education and Renewal, 1988-1991 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - World Council of Churches: Programme Unit on Education and Renewal, Regional Education Secretaries Meeting, Geneva, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - World Council of Churches: Programme Unit on Faith and Witness, 1977-1987 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - World Council of Churches: Programme Unit on Justice and Service, 1987-1991 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - World Council of Churches: Programme Unit on Justice and Service, 1988-1990 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - World Council of Churches: Programme Unit on Justice and Service, Glion Consultation, "Conditions for Sharing", 1977 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - World Council of Churches: Resource Sharing (1 of 2), 1982-1985 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - World Council of Churches: Resource Sharing (2of 2), 1982-1985 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - World Council of Churches/Roman Catholic Church: Joint Working Group, 1963-1986 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - World Council of Churches, "Struggle to be Human", 1972-1973 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - World Council of Churches: Urban Industrial Mission, 1971-1972 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - World Council of Churches, Urban Industrial Mission (1 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - World Council of Churches: Urban Industrial Mission (2 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - World Council of Churches: World Consultation for Leaders of Lay Training, Bossey, Switzerland, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - World Council of Churches/CCA Workshop on Contextual Liturgy & Music, Tainan Theological Seminary, Taiwan (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - World Council of Churches/CCA Workshop on Contextual Liturgy & Music, Tainan Theological Seminary, Taiwan (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - World Methodist Council, 1974-1978 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - World Methodist Council, 1979-1985 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - World Student Christian Federation, 1985-1990 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - World Student Christian Federation, 1999-2001 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - World Student Christian Federation: 27th General Assembly, Colombo, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - World Student Christian Federation: Asia Committee Meetings: Bangkok, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 1969-1970 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - World Student Christian Federation: Asia Committee Meetings, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - World Student Christian Federation: Asia Pacific Regional Committee, Tokyo (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - World Student Christian Federation: Asia Pacific Regional Committee, Tokyo (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - World Student Christian Federation: Asia Regional Consultation on Frontier Internship Project, Hong Kong, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - World Student Christian Federation: Correspondence, 1971-1978 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - World Student Christian Federation: Frontier Internship in Mission, 1976-1979 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - World Student Christian Federation: Frontier Internship in Mission, Asia Committee Meeting, Hong Kong, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - World Student Christian Federation: Papers, 1970-1978 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - World Student Christian Federation/CCA: Joint Programme, 1983-1987 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - World Student Christian Federation/CCA: Joint Programme, Programme Report, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 18-19)
  - Young Christian Workers, 1984, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Young Men's Christian Association: Leaders Conference, Singapore, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Young Men's Christian Association/Young Women's Christian Association, 1966-1973 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Compilation of correspondence with various regional ecumenical organizations, 1991-1995 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Asian Christian Study Conference - "The Social Goals of New Asia", Indonesia, 1957 (Box 105, Folder 17)
- Audio Visual Materials, Series VIII
  - VHS tapes
    - Labeled sequence
      - 1. In the Name of Medicine (English), No date; 1 (Box 68, Folder 1, Item barcode 39002098996581)
      - 4. The 8th Assembly Christian Conference of Asia, 1985; 1 (Box 68, Folder 2, Item barcode 39002098996672)
      - 7. Silent Cries Untold Stories of Migrant Workers in Malaysia, No date; 1 (Box 68, Folder 3, Item barcode 39002098996664)
      - 9. Cry for Justice (Produced by Aboriginal and Islander Commission of the Australian Council of Churches), 1992; 1 (Box 68, Folder 4, Item barcode 39002098996557)
      - 12. Justice in Peace, No date; 1 (Box 68, Folder 5, Item barcode 39002098996615)
      - 15. Vincent Cheng and the Marxist Nework, No date; 1 (Box 68, Folder 6, Item barcode 39002098996722)
      - 18. Into Darkest Borneo; Blowpipes and Bulldozers; Dateline's 28.8.88, 1988; 1 (Box 68, Folder 7, Item barcode 39002098996599)
      - 21. Dalit Indigenous People: A Meeting Point, No date; 1 (Box 68, Folder 8, Item barcode 39002098996565)
      - 23, Two Stories of Development, No date; 1 (Box 68, Folder 9, Item barcode 39002098996714)
    - Additional tapes
      - Women's Ordination- The Hidden Tradition, No date; 1 (Box 69, Folder 1, Item barcode 39002098996862)
      - Pacific Ecumenical Forum, 1990; 1 (Box 69, Folder 2, Item barcode 39002098996839)
      - First Consultation of Asian Christian Women Artists, Hong Kong, volume 1, 1992; 1 (Box 69, Folder 3, Item barcode 39002098996763)
      - First Consultation of Asian Christian Women Artists, volume 4, 1992; 1 (Box 69, Folder 4, Item barcode 39002098996797)
      - Ngapali Workshop; Bakun, No date (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Amnesty International in Asia; Seminary in Urdu Language "Religious Minorities in Pakistan Social and State Oppression" 1992, 1992, no date (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - That They May Have Life; Korean Culture, No date (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Religious Education Conference of Asia; The 146-Year-Long Cry of Okinawa Citizens, 1990, no date (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Untitled (3), no date (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Untitled (3), no date (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Audiocassette tapes
    - Intervox (45 tapes), 1978-1982 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - First Asian Women Christian Artists Consultation, Hong Kong (23 tapes), 1992 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - CCA Women, Hong Kong (6 tapes), 1992 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - CCA 8th Assembly, Seoul (6 tapes), 1985 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - CCA meeting (10 tapes), 1995 November (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Asian Lawyers for Justice and Human Rights (7 tapes), no date (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Bible studies and meeting presentations, no date (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous consultations and presentations, 1978-1990 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      Including "Bishop K H Ting on Theological Education in China", "CCA Women's Concerns", "Struggle in Silence -Women Migrant Workers in H.K.", "From Sisters to Sisters", "Service of Prayer for Peace in the Middle East - Radio New Zealand", "Lay Training in Taiwan"
    - Asian church music, no date (Box 71, Folder 3)
      Including "Mahima CNI Silver Jubilee Christmas Special", "New Korean Hymns", "Asian Hymns from the CCA Hymnal", "Stirred Not Shaken - Firewomen", "A Festival of Asian Christmas Music"
    - Tape and slide set: "Do You Know the Word 'Shame'?", no date (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Photographs
    - Vietnam consultation (1965); Continuation Committee meeting, Hong Kong (1966); WCCE/EACC meetings (1966-1967); EACC 4th Assembly, Bangkok (1968), 1965-1968 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - EACC Film Evangelization Workshop, 1971 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Individuals, meetings, workshops, 1971-1977 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - WCC Central Committee meeting, Utrecht, 1972 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - EACC/CCA 5th Assembly, Singapore, 1973 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - CCA 6th Assembly, Penang, 1977 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Individuals, including CCA staff, Ron O'Grady, Masao Takenaka, 1970s (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Activities, including Asian Christian Service, Youth Resources Conference, Consultation on Evangelism, 1970s (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Worship workshop, Manila, 1981 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Workshop on the Role of Religion in National Harmony, Sri Lanka, 1981 (Box 180, Folder 9a)
    - Family Consultation, Malang, Indonesia, 1982 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - CCA 8th Assembly, Seoul, 1985 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Opening of CCA office in Osaka, 1988 (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - China trip, 1988 (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - CCA workshop "Women Struggle for Justice and Peace," Gurukul, India, 1989 (Box 180, Folder 14)
    - Theological Consultation with Women's Desk, CTC, 1989 (Box 180, Folder 15)
    - Consultation of NCC Women Secretaries, Lahore, 1990 (Box 180, Folder 16)
    - Grassroot Women's Leadership Formation Programme (GWOLF), Penang, 1990 (Box 180, Folder 17)
    - CCA Programme Committee, Malaysia; URM National Coordinators, 1991 (Box 180, Folder 18)
    - CAA Women's Concerns workshops: Developing Leadership, Pakistan and Indonesia, 1991 (Box 180, Folder 19)
    - CAA Women's Concerns workshop: Developing Leadership, Thailand, 1992 (Box 180, Folder 20)
    - CAA Women's Concerns workshop: Developing Leadership, Seoul, Korea, 1992 (Box 180, Folder 21)
    - New CCA Centre in Shatin, Hong Kong, 1993 (Box 180, Folder 22)
    - Ecumenical Leadership Workshop in India - A Joint Training Programme by CCA and AICCW, New Delhi, 1993 (Box 180, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous gatherings, including Consultation on Education for Justice, Madras, India, 1993 (Box 180, Folder 24)
    - CCA-URM Programme Committee, Karachi, Pakistan, URM Leadership Formation Program, PGI Assembly in Irian Jaya, 1994 (Box 180, Folder 25)
    - Asian Ecumenical Course, Hong Kong; Second Line Leadership Formation Programme II, Quezon City, Philippines; Ecumenical Partners Meeting, Hong Kong, 1994 (Box 180, Folder 26)
    - CCA General Committee meeting, Sydney, 1994 (Box 180, Folder 27)
    - CCA 10th Assembly, Colombo, 1995 (Box 180, Folder 28)
    - Asian Church Leaders Consultation on Indo-China, Cambodia, 1995 (Box 180, Folder 29)
    - CCA meetings in Hong Kong, including General Committee, Presidium, signing of CCA company document, 1995 (Box 180, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous gatherings, including farewell to Tosh Arai, South-Asia NCCs Consultation, 1996 (Box 180, Folder 31)
    - Asian Ecumenical Committee meeting, Colombo; WCC Asia and Pacific Joint Worship Group, Tahiti; Consultation on Refugees and Churches' Responses, Madras, 1997 (Box 180, Folder 32)
    - China visit; General Secretaries of Regional Ecumenical Organizations and WCC, Quito; CCA at Harare Assembly, 1998 (Box 180, Folder 33)
    - Asian Ecumenical Course meetings in Bali and Bangkok, CCA Christian-Muslim Dialogue on Human Rights Solidarity; NCC General Secretaries meeting, New Delhi, 1998 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous gatherings including Curriculum and Worship Consultation, Bali; CCA 11th Assembly Preparatory Committee; Mission Round Table, Hong Kong, 1999 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Pre-Assembly Women's Forum, Indonesia, 2000 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Asian Ecumenical Course, Indonesia, 2000 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - CCA 11th General Assembly, Tomohon, Indonesia, 2000 (Box 181, Folder 5-7)
    - Asian Ecumenical Course, Kerala, India, 2001 (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Asian Religious Educators Forum, Chiang Mai, Thailand, 2001 (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Asia Ecumenical Academy, Chiang Mai, Thailand, 2004 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - Asia Ecumenical Academy, Chiang Mai, Thailand, 2005 (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - Women's Forum, Philippines, No date (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - Workshop on worship and music, Tainan, No date (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous photos used in CCA News, No date (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - Albums of photos related to Asian Christian Service, No date (Box 181, Folder 15-18)
  - Slides
    - Slide set and script: "Struggle in Silence: Women Migrant Workers in Hong Kong", No date (Box 181, Folder 19)
    - Slide set and resource packet: "Breaking the Silence: The Church and Domestic Violence", 1986 (Box 181, Folder 20)
    - Slide set with captions re. Asian Church Women's Conference, 6th Assembly, Japan, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Slide set with script "In the Bosom of Struggle", No date (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Boxed slides re. 3rd Sub-regional Workshop, 1992 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Boxed slide set "From Sisters to Sisters", No date (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Boxed slide set "Jesus With Us Today" (Korean), 1988 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Slide set "By the Mekong River", No date (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Slide set re. women's concerns, No date (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Slide sets - unidentified, No date (Box 182, Folder 8-10)
    - Boxed slides - unidentified, No date (Box 182, Folder 11)
- Financial Records, Series IX
  This series is predominately composed of financial reports, correspondence, donors and grants, and materials relating to the purchase and renovation of the Lutheran Theological Seminary in Hong Kong. Financial reports include auditor reports, budgets, and programme income and expenditure reports. This series also includes Finance Committee papers, including correspondence and programme summaries with budget planning materials. Donor and grant materials contain correspondence and agreements with donor agencies, including ICCO and UN-ESCAP, Bread for the World, and others. Materials relating to the purchase and renovation of the Lutheran Theological Seminary include official documents and correspondence, funding requests, building renovation plans, diagrams and photographs, a structural survey report, and costs.
  - CCA General Finance
    - CCA company registration, 1993-1996 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - CCA incorporation, 1996-1999 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - CCA Staff Salary Committee, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Finance Committee Papers, 1983-1988 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Finance Committee Papers, 1990-1991 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Finance Committee Papers, 1992-1996 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, financial audits, 1993-1999 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, general, 1961-1969 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, general, 1970-1989 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, general, 1980-1989 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, general, 1990-1993 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, general, 1994-1995 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - CCA Donors Book, 1974-1975 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Donors and Grants
    - Correspondence, donors, 1987-1994 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, donors, 1997-2001 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Australia, 1984-1994 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Germany, 1981, 1986-1994 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Germany, 1999-2001 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Netherlands - ICCO, 1983-1990 (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Netherlands - ICCO, 1991-1994 (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - Norway, Sweden, Denmark, 1987-1994 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - UN-ESCAP, 1994-1996 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - UN-ESCAP, 2000 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - UN-ESCAP-CCA Training Programme for Trainers, 1993-1996 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records and Reports
    - Draft budget and funding request, 1995-1996 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Draft budget and funding request, 1996-1997 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1965-1969 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1970-1972 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1973-1974 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1975-1976 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1977-1979 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1980-1982 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1983-1984 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1987 (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1988 (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1991 (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1992-1993 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1994-1996 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 1997-1999 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Financial Reports and budget, 2000-2005 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Financial Reports, multi-year, 1985-2005 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Hong Kong Inland Revenue, 1990-1996 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Purchase and Renovation of Lutheran Theological Seminary
    - Building renovation correspondence and Contracts, 1992-1994 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Building renovation photographs, 1992-1993 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Building renovation plans and diagrams, 1993 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - CCA Hong Kong Registration, 1992-1996 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Colliers Jardine reports on purchase and rental options for CCA, 1991-1992 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Collier Jardine re renovations (includes building layouts), 1992 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, general, 1991 May-1992 August (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, general, 1992 September-1994 June (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Housing Committee, 1991-1995, 1997 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence with donor organizations, 1991 August-1992 May (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence with donor organizations, 1992 June-1995 June (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Housing and Office Project budget, reports, 1991-1996 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Structural Survey Report on Lutheran Theological Seminary Campus, 1992 February-March (Box 125, Folder 19)